Hi, my name is Rosario Nene Ortega.
I'm a Dance instructor, Ballroom and Tango, at the Goddess Store in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip, we are goin to talk about the Promenade, Promenade and the American Tango.
So we start in the dance position okay, we are facing our partner.
Our party is going to let us know that we are going to move in a Promenade and we open our body.
I'm opening, I'm going to the right.
So, I am going to step one, two, three, quick, quick, and close.
Okay, I'm going to show this again.
Let's start from the beginning.
So I"m going to turn and open my body.
I'm going to Promenade.
I'm going to take a walk.
That's in translation from the French Promenade.
So it's one.
two, tan-go, close.
When I close, I go back and face my partner.
This is a Tango Promenade in the American Tango, okay.
So, let's take it from the back!
See how it looks.
I'm going to start form this angle.
It's going to go, turn to the right.
See I'm already showing that I'm going to Promenade and slow and slow, quick, quick, slow.
This is a Promenade, Rosario Ortega at the Goddess Store in Hollywood, Florida.